# BARIŞ BABAHAN

Front end Developer

#### DETAILS

#### PHONE

05488794949

#### **EMAIL**

babahaninfo@gmail.com

# LINKS

LinkedIn

My personal website

Github

# SKILLS

React

HTML & CSS

Git

Docker

JIRA

Agile Methodology

Bitbucket

Node.js

MongoDB

# **PROFILE**

I'm a currently software engineering student at Eastern Mediterranean University and going to graduate in the summer of 2022. I choose my profession to be a Front-end developer for time being I have not very much experience in Back-end. In 5 years my goal is to learn Back-end and database.

# **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

#### Front-end Developer, Archis academy

Eskisehir

Sep 2020 - Present

I'm a Front-end developer at Archis academy. I'm trying my best to implement designs as pixel-perfect. Besides my work, I'm helping trainees in Archis. I share my knowledge and prepare them to get ready for our main project.

#### Team Lead, Archis academy

Eskişehir

Mar 2021 - May 2021

Archis was going to make a Hackathon event called Endurance. The goal was to implement our newly designed website ASAP. I was the leader of 3 people, helping them to finish their tasks by reviewing their PR's and explaining task tickets.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Software engineering, Eastern Mediterranean University

Nicosia

Jun 2017 - Jun 2022

- · Learning data structure and analysis of the algorithms.
- · Improving analytical mindset.
- · Improving communication and collaboration.